const questions = [
  {
    id: 'q1',
    question: 'Please provide your Finnish business ID.',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'A Finnish business ID is a unique identifier for businesses in Finland. Example: 1234567-8.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: 1234567-8',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid business ID.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q2',
    question: 'Is this your business information?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Confirm whether the provided information pertains to your business.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'singleChoice',
    answerOptions: 'Yes, No',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
    optionalStepAnswer: 'Is this correct?',
  },
  {
    id: 'q3',
    question:
      "How much of the company's own free capital are you prepared to use for development and internationalization in the next 12 months?",
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Own free capital refers to capital that does not have a repayment obligation, such as accumulated profits and investments made in the company (e.g., invested unrestricted equity fund - SVOP).',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'slider',
    answerOptions: '0, 100000, 10000,',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
    unit: 'EUR',
  },
  {
    id: 'q4',
    question: 'What is your company’s annual turnover?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Annual turnover refers to the total revenue generated by your company in a year.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: 500000',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid annual turnover.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q5',
    question: 'Which of the following services does your company use?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip: 'Select all the services that your company currently utilizes.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'multiChoice',
    answerOptions:
      'Accounting, Legal, Marketing, IT Support, Human Resources, Customer Service, Sales, Logistics, Procurement, Research and Development',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
  },
  {
    id: 'q6',
    question: 'What is the primary industry of your business?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip: 'Specify the main industry in which your business operates.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: Information Technology',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid industry.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q7',
    question:
      'Do you have a dedicated research and development (R&D) department?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Indicate whether your company has a department specifically for research and development.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'singleChoice',
    answerOptions: 'Yes, No',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
  },
  {
    id: 'q8',
    question: 'How many employees does your company have?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip: 'Provide the total number of employees working in your company.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: 50',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid number of employees.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q9',
    question:
      'What percentage of your revenue is reinvested into the business annually?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Specify the percentage of your company’s revenue that is reinvested into the business each year.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'slider',
    answerOptions: '0, 100, 1',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
    unit: '%', // Added unit
  },
  {
    id: 'q10',
    question: 'Which regions does your company operate in?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip: 'Select all the regions where your company has operations.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'multiChoice',
    answerOptions:
      'North America, Europe, Asia, Africa, South America, Australia',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
  },
  {
    id: 'q11',
    question: 'What is the primary goal of your business for the next year?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Specify the main objective your business aims to achieve in the upcoming year.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: Increase market share by 10%',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid goal.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q12',
    question: 'Does your company have an environmental sustainability policy?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Indicate whether your company has a policy focused on environmental sustainability.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'singleChoice',
    answerOptions: 'Yes, No',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
  },
  {
    id: 'q13',
    question: 'What is your company’s customer satisfaction rate?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Provide the percentage of customers who are satisfied with your company’s products or services.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: 85%',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid customer satisfaction rate.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q14',
    question: 'How much does your company spend on marketing annually?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip: 'Specify the total annual expenditure on marketing activities.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: 20000',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid amount.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q15',
    question:
      'Which of the following best describes your company’s growth strategy?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Select the option that best describes your company’s approach to growth.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'singleChoice',
    answerOptions:
      'Organic Growth, Mergers and Acquisitions, Partnerships, Franchising',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
  },
  {
    id: 'q16',
    question: 'What percentage of your workforce is involved in remote work?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip: 'Specify the percentage of employees who work remotely.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'slider',
    answerOptions: '0, 100, 1',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
    unit: '%',
  },
  {
    id: 'q17',
    question: 'Which of the following technologies does your company use?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Select all the technologies that your company currently utilizes.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'multiChoice',
    answerOptions:
      'Cloud Computing, Artificial Intelligence, Blockchain, Internet of Things',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
  },
  {
    id: 'q18',
    question: 'What is the average age of your company’s employees?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Provide the average age of the employees working in your company.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: 35',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid age.',
  },
  {
    id: 'q19',
    question: 'Does your company offer employee stock options?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Indicate whether your company provides stock options to its employees.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: '',
    answerType: 'singleChoice',
    answerOptions: 'Yes, No',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: '',
  },
  {
    id: 'q20',
    question: 'What is the primary source of funding for your business?',
    condition: '',
    tooltip:
      'Specify the main source of financial support for your business operations.',
    syntaxPlaceholder: 'Example: Venture Capital',
    answerType: 'directInput',
    answerOptions: '',
    targetAudience: 'Everyone',
    errorAnswer: 'Please provide a valid source of funding.',
  },
];

export default questions;
